=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 1=
= My Fairy Doctor = = الحلقة 1 =
(Minghe Ancient Town)
(مدينة مينغي القديمة)
(National Medical Centre)
(المركز الطبي الوطني)
My name is Tang Qizi,
اسمي تانغ كيزي ،
the 52nd generation of the Tang family of traditional Chinese medicine.
الجيل 52 من عائلة تانغ للطب الصيني التقليدي.
Tang family has been a family of doctors
كانت عائلة تانغ عائلة من الأطباء
for generations since the Tang Dynasty.
لأجيال منذ عهد أسرة تانغ.
(National Medical Centre) However, my father,
(المركز الطبي الوطني) لكن أبي ،
an narrow-minded man, is rigid
رجل ضيق الأفق صارم
and inflexible,
وغير مرن ،
unlike me.
خلافا لي.
When it comes to making money from medical treatment,
عندما يتعلق الأمر بجني الأموال من العلاج الطبي ،
I have a brilliant way of doing it.
لدي طريقة رائعة للقيام بذلك.
(Tang Qizi) Are you...
(تانغ كيزي) هل أنت ...
pregnant?
حامل؟
Nonsense!
كلام فارغ!
I'm still a virgin!
ما زلت عذراء!
(Tang Badou) Who is that girl in your arms?
(تانغ بادو) من تلك الفتاة بين ذراعيك؟
I'm helping my niece
أنا أساعد ابنة أخي
getting some cold medicine.
الحصول على بعض الأدوية الباردة.
And you call me sick?
وأنت تدعوني مريض؟
You're the ones who are sick.
أنتم المرضى.
You are really sick.
أنت مريض حقا.
Believe it.
صدقه.
Tell me then.
اخبرني لاحقا.
What illness do I have?
ما مرضي؟
Have you recently had a bitter taste in your mouth
هل كان لديك مؤخرًا طعم مر في فمك
and ulcers on your lips?
وتقرحات على شفتيك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Severe dizziness,
دوخة شديدة
sleep disorders
اضطرابات النوم
and swollen tongue.
وتورم اللسان.
Indeed.
في الواقع.
Your disease
مرضك
may seem common,
قد يبدو شائعًا ،
but it is very dangerous.
لكنها خطيرة جدا.
The incubation period is long.
فترة الحضانة طويلة.
Once it breaks out,
بمجرد أن ينفجر ،
it could...
ممكن...
kill you.
أقتلك.
What?
ماذا؟
Then what should I do?
إذن ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
Miss.
يغيب.
The price of consultation
ثمن الاستشارة
and prescription is separately charged.
والوصفات الطبية يتم احتسابها بشكل منفصل.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Dr. Tang.
دكتور.  كماشة.
Please help me.
الرجاء مساعدتي.
Here are the medicines.
ها هي الأدوية.
Make sure to take them regularly.
تأكد من تناولها بانتظام.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you, Dr. Tang.
شكرا لك دكتور تانغ.
I'll boil them when I get home.
سأغليهم عندما أصل إلى المنزل.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Goodbye, miss.
وداعا يا آنسة.
Bye.
وداعا.
Qizi.
بنت.
How did you know she's sick?
كيف عرفت أنها مريضة؟
I saw her licking her lips all the time
رأيتها تلعق شفتيها طوال الوقت
and figured she must have an ulcer on her mouth.
ورأت أنها تعاني من قرحة في فمها.
It is actually just a symptom of excess heat.
إنه في الواقع مجرد عرض من أعراض الحرارة الزائدة.
Brilliant, Tang Qizi.
الرائعة ، تانغ كيزي.
You made it sound so serious.
لقد جعلتها تبدو خطيرة للغاية.
Of course.
بالطبع.
That's how I make money.
هذه هي الطريقة التي أجني بها المال.
Is Dr. Tang around?
هل الدكتور تانغ موجود؟
Yes.
نعم.
(Tang Yide)
(تانغ ييد)
Father.
أب.
Why are you
لماذا انت
back early?
العودة مبكرا؟
(Tang Qizi.)
(تانغ كيزي.)
(Ancestral Virtues) (You shall kneel)
(فضائل الأجداد) (تركع)
(and reflect on yourself in front of the ancestors.)
(وفكر في نفسك أمام الأجداد).
(Don't get up before dawn.)
(لا تستيقظ قبل الفجر).
You punish me,
أنت تعاقبني ،
then I'll steal your wine.
ثم سأسرق النبيذ الخاص بك.
Hey,
يا،
ancestors.
أسلاف.
You were all professional
كنتم كلكم محترفون
and respectable,
ومحترمة ،
but why did you bring up
لكن لماذا تربيت
such an narrow-minded man like my father?
مثل هذا الرجل ضيق الأفق مثل والدي؟
(Deceased, Tang Mingwen) He wouldn't let me see patients
(متوفى ، تانغ مينجوين) لم يسمح لي برؤية المرضى
or go abroad with Nianzhou for further studies.
أو اذهب إلى الخارج مع Nianzhou لمزيد من الدراسات.
So please
إذن من فضلك
come out
يظهر
and talk to him.
والتحدث معه.
Please forgive
أرجوك سامحني
my rudeness.
فظاظتي.
Ancestors, please forgive me.
الأجداد ، أرجوك سامحوني.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Dabao.
داباو.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Why did this painting fall off?
لماذا سقطت هذه اللوحة؟
Is the jade pendant on the painting glowing?
هل قلادة اليشم على اللوحة متوهجة؟
Am I drunk?
هل انا سكران
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض